{
    "subject": "resource/V/Line_G_class",
    "predicate": "ontology/owner",
    "object": "resource/AWB_Limited",
    "human_readable": "The owner of V/Line G-class is AWB Limited.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8717053532600403,
            "question": "Who owns the V/Line G-class?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6903840899467468,
            "question": "What type of rail vehicle is owned by AWB Limited?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.646742045879364,
            "question": "What might be the purpose of owning a V/Line G-class?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5460813045501709,
            "question": "What other types of vehicles does AWB Limited own?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5063043236732483,
            "question": "Is AWB Limited involved in the transportation industry?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.31129536032676697,
            "question": "Where might you find a V/Line G-class train?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2729372978210449,
            "question": "Are there different classes of V/Line trains?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2344878613948822,
            "question": "What does 'V/Line' likely refer to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1038254126906395,
            "question": "What are some characteristics of a G-class train?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.04455358907580376,
            "question": "Can you name other companies that own rail vehicles?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The owner of V/Line G-class is AWB Limited.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2916_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some characteristics of a G-class train?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2916_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What does 'V/Line' likely refer to?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2916_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there different classes of V/Line trains?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2916_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2916_101.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2916_103.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2916_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2916_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2916_61.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2916_65.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2916_73.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2916_78.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2916_80.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2916_93.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\nThe documents state that Freight Australia, a private company, purchased the locomotives after the sale of V/Line Freight. There is no mention of AWB Limited owning the locomotives.  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "After analyzing the context information, I can tell that there is no direct mention of AWB Limited as the owner of V/Line G-class. However, ATN Access was created to service AWB Limited with its logistical difficulties.\n\nTherefore, my response would be:\n\n`{'output': 'no'}`"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents do not provide information supporting that the owner of V/Line G-class locomotives was AWB Limited. Instead, it mentions the formation of ATN Access and the use of L class locomotives for running trains in Victoria to assist with logistical difficulties related to AWB Limited. There is no direct statement or implication regarding ownership transfer to AWB Limited specifically from V/Line Freight."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"no\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 0,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}